I used to roller skate all the time.
过去我总溜旱冰.
I loved it when I was little.Did you?
小时候我就特别喜欢溜旱冰. 你呢?
No.I went straight from my pram to a surfboard.
No. 我下了婴儿车就直接到冲浪板上去了.
I used to live in the ocean.
我过去一直是在海上生活的.
No wheels required.
不需要轮子.
Well,you're the first surfing physicist I've ever met.
Well, 你是我所遇到的第一位会冲浪的物理学家.
Oh,right.
Oh, right.
Dean told you I used to be a physicist,didn't he?
Dean告诉过你我以前是个物理学家,是不是?
Yes.
It's an interesting combination.
这真是个有趣的组合.
I like interesting combinations.
我喜欢有趣的组合.
A surfing,bartending physicist is very interesting.
一个会冲浪的, 在酒吧工作的物理学家, 实在很有意思.
Elena told you.
Elena告诉你了.
Elena told me.
Elena告诉我了.
I'm sorry.I didn't mean any harm,Heather.
很抱歉. 我没有任何恶意, Heather.
That's OK.
没关系.
I like a man with a vivid imagination.
我喜欢想象力丰富的人.
That's good.
那太好了.
I like someone with a sense of humor.
我喜欢有幽默感的人.
But why would you tell someone you were a physicist?
但为什么你总是告诉别人你过去是个物理学家呢?
Well,I used to say I was a doctor.
Well, 我过去一直说我是一名医生.
You didn't.
不可能吧!
But people asked me for medical advice.
但人们向我请教医学方面的知识.